It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away. The great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you. Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow. Go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life. It's your life.
Shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of day.
You make my day every day.
He's a revolutionary? Army buddy? Correct.
Hey, Luffy. Wait.
No need to wake him up.
I just came to see him before I go.
Go?
So soon? Yeah.
There's some trouble heading
towards Dressrosa as we speak.
Who's trouble?
It's CP0.
Remember the Doflamingo mix-up?
They played a key role in it.
I'd be real cautious.
They're coming for us.
Things are gonna get a bit crazy
around here in a day or two.
It'd be in your best interest to hit the
road as soon as possible. We appreciate.
it thank you I'm still kind of shocked
that Luffy has another brother right it's
the first I heard of it that figures I
think it surprised Luffy most of all you
want to follow up on that one many years
ago I was presumed to
be dead Luffy Ace and
were inseparable, running amok
and raising all sorts of hell.
In the city, in the forest, anywhere.
Ol' Garp would try his
best to keep us in line.
but we wanted to grow up and be pirates.
We made a vow and became brothers
by sharing some sake together.
But one day, I was
involved in a bad accident.
Or rather, a bad incident.
Ace! Luffy!
There's something wrong with this town!
Something wrong with these people!
They know people are gonna die!
They're happy people are going to die!
They're sick!
This whole place is sick!
I can't stay here any longer!
I have to tell them right now!
Luffy! Ace! Run!
What happened to you, boy?
Hightown wreaks worse than
Grey Terminal ever did.
The people act civilized, but on
the inside, they're all rotten.
They only care about making themselves
look good no matter what it takes.
I can't stay here.
If I do, then I'll never be free.
Don't worry, guys. I'm fine.
I just wish I could see you.
Even once.
It looks nice from the outside,
but this house is a birdcage.
I'm gonna lose my mind if I have to
stay in this stuffy, stuck-up place.
I thought I found freedom, but
it seems to keep slipping away.
Ace, we'll be...
Help me.
Somebody, please, help.
You certainly kept me waiting. What
could be more important than me?
Sorry, oh goodness, is that
that boy's in rough shape?
Hey, hurt boy, help!
Get the medic, prepare treatment! Go!
He's awake!
Don't startle the poor thing.
Give me a break.
I wasn't trying to.
Rude, you big ol' meaty.
What the...
Where am I?
You were on board our ship.
It says Sabo on all your belongings.
I'm guessing that's your name.
Sabo?
I don't know.
That can't be right.
Well, then what is your name, boy?
No idea.
Think he lost his memory? Perhaps.
You're telling me the kid
doesn't remember a thing?
No, not even his own name.
Well, I found the boy washed up ashore.
Over in the highland of the Goa kingdom.
I'm sure that means he's
got some noble blood in him.
I bet you his parents are worried sick.
We should take him back.
No thanks.
Don't bother. Why not?
I don't know why.
I just have a feeling
telling me not to go.
So you're telling me you didn't get
your memories back until two years ago?
Yeah.
I'm surprised they came
back to you at all.
Kinda weird, isn't it?
I actually have Ace to
think for that. Huh? Huh?
Or that's what I believe.
It happened in the worst
possible way, though.
That tragedy...
is what awakened my memories.
What's going on, oh?
It's the second in command—perfect timing.
Follow us to the situation room.
The war in marine four just ended.
We're on our way to a
briefing about it right now.
I
think one of the four emperors is down.
Where's Eva? They okay?
It doesn't say—not here.
not here The only reported
deaths are the Emperor,
Whitebeard, and Firefist Ace, too.
Hey, Dragon, read this.
Wait, that can't be true.
It says here that you're
Straw Hat Luffy's father.
That's correct.
I'll
be so
tough that
all the other pirates
and all the marines will bow at my feet.
That's gonna be the legacy
I leave behind when I die.
Sabo, are you okay?
you're acting bizarre
let
me tell
you guys
a secret it says Aka Inu punched a hole
right through Ace's chest
all
it takes
to become brothers is to share some Sake,
we'll always be brothers, and
nobody can take that away.
From now on, we're
honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
Brothers!
What's come over you, Sabo?
That's right.
The man who died wasn't
just any old pirate.
It wasn't some dangerous
menace of the great pirate era.
that needed to be stumped out.
Ace is my brother.
You won't catch me running
away, and I'll never lose!
The chief's awake!
Thank goodness!
That's great news!
We all thought you were gonna die!
You big jerk!
You had a really high fever, Sabo.
You've been out for three days straight.
We've been so worried.
You got your memory back?
Yeah, I can remember everything.
Who I am, where I'm from, even the
whole reason I left home and set sail.
I see. I'm glad.
You won't leave, will you?
No, don't worry.
Do you know if Dragon's still around? Yes.
We need to talk.
At that moment, it felt like
Ace took me aside and said,
Hey, you're Sabo, and you're
a brother of mine and Luffy's.
Here I am. Sorry it took
so long, Ace. Take a
look at this you'll be
happy to hear luffy's
well on his way to
becoming the king of the
pirates that's our badass
little brother for you
Hey, Sabo.
I have a favor to ask of
the Revolutionary Army.
There's a Devil Fruit that
I need to get my hands on.
But wait, what about the
flame flame fruit, Mr.
Luffy?
There's one guy I hope
doesn't win, but it's fine.
The lives of my friends matter way more.
Don't you worry about nothing.
Just go and save the day and let old
Bato take care of the tournament for you.
Thanks.
You're awesome, buddy.
If you think you're getting the
Flame Flame Fruit, you're wrong.
Sorry, Luffy. It's mine.
Listen up!
I don't know who the hell you
think you are, but that's Mr.
Luffy to you, you damn punk!
The Flame Flame Fruit belonged
to his brother, Firefist Ace,
so nobody deserves to
have it more than him!
Also, he's gonna be King of the
Pirates one day, you jackass!
I know.
I've known that for years.
Hey, what's your deal?
You show up out of nowhere and
tell me I can't have the fruit?
Luffy, it's me.
Nope, don't know ya.
Listen, that flame flame fruit
belonged to my brother Ace.
So don't get in my way.
I don't know who you're calling Luffy?
You see?
It's real, buddy. My name is Lucy.
Give me some credit.
I would recognize my own brother anywhere.
Your brother?
Listen, pal—only two people
can call me their brother:
ace, and my other brother who died!
died
Liar!
How else would I know we stole booze
from Dadan and shared it together?
Stop!
Where have you been all this time?
Why did you come see me sooner?
I totally thought you were dead!
That means a lot, Luffy.
I'm glad you're alive too, brother.
I'm sorry, Sambo, but I saw Ace die and
I couldn't do anything to help save him.
Yeah, Ace may not be with
us, but at least you're here.
You don't know how grateful I am.
I nearly lost two brothers without
being able to do anything about it.
If something awful happened to you,
then I wouldn't have anyone
else left now, would I?
So thank you.
Thanks for staying alive this whole time.
Luffy!
Would you let me eat the
flame flame fruit then?
I really think it should be yours!
Would you look at that?
Luffy is happy.
Wonder what he's dreaming about right now.
See you around. Oh?
I got to see his face.
All right, this is a fever card of Luffy.
I had one made up.
Huh?
When did that happen?
I'll be taking a piece as well.
All right, I'm sure that Luffy can be a
handful, but keep an eye on it for me.
Yeah, you bet, you pal.
Funny, I remember Ace
saying the same exact thing.
Sabo, this is Hack.
Hey, I just left the house. Coming.
Roger that.
And how was Luffy?
He seemed like he was quite a...
Galick.
Why did he hang up, the papa's ass?
Whoa, I'm not Sabo!
So, are we pretty much good to go?
Yes, anytime. Nice.
Once we get back to Baratie, there's so
much I want to tell Dragon about Luffy.
Till next time.
It was nice to see you again.
Let's hurry!
Be my eyes, would you?
What did it come up?
One, sir.
So be it, then.
Seems the odds are in Straw Hat's favor.
It's what we agreed on, right?
It is, but...
Then I'd say he won this
round fair and square.
There will be no arrests tonight.
You're not serious.
Isho, please.
We worked hard to find them.
And you let them go over a dice roll?
And after lashing out at
the Fleet Admiral, too?
This is going to be our best chance
to bring in Law and the Straw Hats.
Hold on, Maynard.
You should know better
than to take a gamble.
than complain about the outcome of a role.
It's quite unbecoming of a man.
Has anyone seen Lucy after the tournament?
Not that I'm aware of.
I want to at least thank him.
He's probably just laying low.
Whether they're pirates or criminals,
it doesn't change the fact
that they're our saviors.
and we owe them everything.
Grandfather!
Yes, Rebecca?
I haven't been able to find
Father Lucy or the others yet.
Yes, no need to worry.
Kiros has already contacted me.
They are all safe together.
That aside, Rebecca.
Should I agree to return to the throne?
You do understand that
we'll make you a princess.
Unbelievable.
To think after all the effort it
took to escape Big Mom's ship.
Why would you want to
make any more trouble?
What makes you think you get a vote?
Quit whining!
I'm saying this is a
warning to your crew—you
shouldn't stick your
nose into their affairs.
I wanted to wait for the ship quietly,
but no, you just had to go rushing ahead.
Shut up and do what I tell you to.
Can you handle that?
Because I can crush your heart
and not lose any sleep over it.
Fine,
but I don't like it coming
to shore—was the best idea?
There's still a chance we can save them,
but we need you to cooperate with us.
If I'm so important,
perhaps you should be nicer.
What was that?
Haven't
you taunted me enough?
We need to hurry!
I'll take as much time as I see fit.
Noisy raccoon—I'm a reindeer pal,
as if there's any difference?
Of course there is now.
Shut up and let's go!
Listen—if they die, I'm gonna
make sure you pay for it.
We need your help, so move your butt.
so move your butt
Whoa, it's really hard
to run on this ground.
I wish we hadn't been separated
from Sanji and the others.
This is awful.
We were too focused on
that mysterious girl.
Oh, Nami, I'll help you.
I'll help myself, thank you.
Oh!
Oh, Tim will be as bad as I am!
Look out!
They're coming! Huh?
Yee-haw!
Too bad, huh?
We caught ya.
Now, tell us where you
hid the young lady. Huh?
And how'd you invaders
get onto this island?
Answer me!
Not just anyone could... Huh?
What?
Oh dear, what is it now?
Here comes a rain rupture!
Again?
Take cover!
What's going on here?
Is it raining?
No, it's more like a geyser!
I'll protect you,
whatever may happen to me!
Nami!
Mama Nozki!
Help me!
I'm drowning!
Dad!
You Devil Fruit guys are so delicate!
I'm going on my!
I'm useless to you now!
Hey, get back here!
You damn invaders!
Come on, don't just lay there.
You're a real lifesaver.
You get it too, Momo.
Thank you so much.
Ask questions later.
Kill for now.
Yeah!
Look, be careful.
This time, I can protect you.
Allow me to take care of him.
Huh.
Don't get cocky.
Slousy corn, go!
What's with his arms?
How far, full?
Come on, man!
Gladly.
Soul parade!
Oh, Bokiji's so brave!
What kind of a birdie is this?
Brook!
Keep him occupied!
Huh? Huh?
Diablo!
Mutom! Mallet!
Master Sheep's Head, no!
Hey, Sanji!
Ah, Nami, my sweet!
Who are you monsters?
Took the words right out of my...
What a creep.
Miss Jinrami!
All of you, retreat now!
Master Sheep's Head has been defeated.
But we haven't found the samurai yet.
He hasn't shown himself even
after we pushed them this far.
Go report that there's
no samurai here, right?
The water's draining.
Wonder what that was all about?
This place is rather odd.
I hope that girl's okay too.
She moves faster than we
do, so I'm sure she's fine.
Good point.
That's Chopper. I'm on it. Let
us make haste. You're right.
We've got no time to lose
What the hell?
They're out cold. Captain!
There's a giant hole! A hole?
Something fell here!
Arm yourselves!
That crater, it's massive.
We could have made this.
Yeah, and who the heck's responsible?
Wait, it's kinda shaped like a tree.
A person that's right,
I did hear a legend once about a sky
island where a great monster lives.
I believe it's somewhere around here, huh?
Let me get this straight: that
thing fell from a sky island.
The impact was so bad it just
capsized one of our ships—capsized it,
who's behind this?
this I'll set them straight.
The strong survive and the weak perish.
That is the way our world has always been.
A few minutes prior.
Well, what do we have
here? I don't know, but we
should leave him alone he
must be crazy we're 30 000
feet high that's not exactly
a short drop this was
a man who was desperately
in search of a place to die
Who am I to stop him?
He'd had an eventful life.
as a pirate he had tasted
defeat seven times and
on 18 separate occasions he'd been
captured by the Navy or enemy ships he'd
spent quite some time as a prisoner and
suffer through torture again and again.
His objective was to take his
own life by the unusual means of
plummeting off the edge of a sky
island and now we
return to the present
to reiterate this is a man who
repeatedly challenged the navy
and the four emperors was captured
18 times and was sentenced to
death 40 times when he was hanged
the chain crumbled into pieces
When he was sent to be beheaded,
the guillotine blade shattered.
when he was to be impaled
the spear broke additionally
he sank a total of nine
prison vessels in other
words no one was capable
of killing him in fact he
was incapable of killing
himself
now
what's happening?
Crap, it really is a monster.
Oh, jeez.
My head hurts.
So I survived again.
Why is it so hard to die?
That daughter in the old
Whitebeard, he pulled it off easy.
The man who longed for a place to
die, King of the Beasts, Kaido.
Those who know of him
have a certain saying.
If it's one-on-one, always bet on Kylo.
Whether on land, at sea, or in the air,
it's a widely held belief
that this terrifying pirate
is more powerful than any
other living creature.
Well, looks like I have no choice.
Damn it all!
Hurry up, Joker!
It's time for the final battle!
Get ready!
If this dreary world
is destroyed, so be it!
Let's start history's greatest war!
Are you with me?